Who dares make me leave? I'm carrying a Jiang heir inside me
That's your grandchild. You'd let it be born out there?
Stop this act. At your age, how could you get pregnant?
We're at a hospital, how could I lie? Please, son, I beg you
I'm already ruined, but the child is the Jiangs' only heir!
In my last life, I was killed over my husband's affair
This life, your whole family will pay in blood
Xiao Lan, come wash my feet. Zhang Guifang!
Don't push it. Oh, my precious son says
he wants Grandma to serve him personally. If she doesn't do it well
he won't come out. We'll all stay in here, let's see who panics
Honey
Honey, calm down. Careful, the baby!
She only tolerates you because you carry a Jiang heir. Sweep away. Something's off
Way off. Jiang Chengao's look... that's not how you look at a daughter-in-law
Gently! I'm carrying your child. Don't crush it